

#### ABOUT ME

Creative Front-End Developer offering 5+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in designing, developing and testing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a Front-End Developer

# Skills

HTML & CSS3:

React:

WordPress:

Creative Suite:

(#:

Sql:

# THEBE SETSHEDI

Address: The Parks lifestyle, Fourways 1684,

Phone: +(27) 78 141 4736

Email: setshedi.thebe@gmail.com

# Experience

web developer (2020 - Now)

- Frontend user interface design backend .net core API
- Train the A.I Product management Develop client websites
- Write and maintain the front-end code of web applications.
- Applies knowledge of industry trends and developments to improve service to our business
- Contribute to the department's ways of working by suggesting, and implementing, continuous improvement initiatives
- Understands standard systems development lifecycle Assist in the design, coding and testing of technical solutions

#### Web developer (2017 - 2020)

- Write and maintain the websites. (Ecommerce Sites, Membership site)
- Create artwork for campaigns Meet up with clients to discuss business rules
- Coordinate internal resources and third parties/vendors for the flawless execution of projects
- Ensure that all projects are delivered on-time, within scope and within budget
- Assist in the definition of project scope and objectives, involving all relevant stakeholders and ensuring technical feasibility Ensure resource availability and allocation

Internship (2016 – 2017) MCSD, MCSA

### Education

Rosebank College (2014 - 2016)

Diploma in Software development

Geelhout Park Secondary School (Matric)

English, Math lit, Accounting, Business Studies, Computer Application Technology